digital-muscle.com 2015-03-13

# Privacy - Digital Muscle

## Business Privacy Policy

This privacy policy sets out how Digital Muscle uses and protects any information that you give digital-muscle.com when you use this website.

Digital-muscle is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.

Digital-muscle may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes. This policy is effective from 01/01/2012.

Digital Muscle Limited is a fully incorporated company both in Hong Kong and Thailand.

Digital-muscle believes that strong electronic privacy is crucial for the ongoing success of the Internet as a service, commercial and entertainment medium. To this end, unless you designate otherwise, the information you enter here will be known to only two parties: Digital-Muscle and yourself. We pledge that Digital-muscle will not release your personal data to anyone else without your consent – period. You may change the status of whether you wish to receive Digital-muscle offers and communications at any time. When we do present information to our advertisers, unless you tell us otherwise, it is in the form of aggregate statistics compiled among all of our visitors’ answers to survey questions as well as grouped on-site behavior.

## What we collect

We may collect the following information:

  * Name and job title
  * Contact information including email address
  * Demographic information such as postcode, preferences and interests
  * Other information relevant to customer surveys and/or offers

## What we do with the information we gather

We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons:

  * Internal record keeping.
  * We may use the information to improve our products and services
  * We may periodically send promotional emails about new products, special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided.
  * From time to time, we may also use your information to contact you for market research purposes. We may contact you by email, phone, fax or mail. We may use the information to customise the website according to your interests.

## Security

We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

## PayPal

If you choose to use PayPal to finalise and pay for your order, you will provide your credit card number directly to Paypal. Paypal’s Privacy policy will apply to the information you provide on the PayPal website.

## 2Checkout Inc.

If you choose to use 2Checkout to pay for your order, you will provide your credit card number directly to 2Checkout. Policies regarding this payment gateway is listed on 2Checkout website.

## Refund Policy

Our website is very particular about any feedback from the purchasers of our products. If you send us a message informing about an error, queries or suggestion you will receive a speedy response from our sales team within 24 working hours. As a general rule of thumb we assist with providing you a solution.

We provide refund of your payment in the following scenarios:

  1. When a customer demands a refund immediately after receiving the service/report.
  2. When a customer informs us about changing his/her decision to buy the service, clearly station the fact that he/she will not be utilising the service’s content after receiving it.
  3. Reasons which prevent a customer from proper usage of the service are stated clearly on our website.

## How we use cookies

A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer’s hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyse web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.

We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyse data about webpage traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system.

Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us.

You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.

## Links to other websites

Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.

## Controlling your personal information

You may choose to restrict the collection or use of your personal information in the following ways:

  * Whenever you are asked to fill in a form on the website, look for the box that you can click to indicate that you do not want the information to be used by anybody for direct marketing purposes
  * If you have previously agreed to us using your personal information for direct marketing purposes, you may change your mind at any time by writing to or emailing us at [sales AT digital-muscle.com]

We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so. We may use your personal information to send you promotional information about third parties which we think you may find interesting if you tell us that you wish this to happen.

If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please write to or email us as soon as possible, at the above address. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect.

## Modification

Digital Muscle as a company has with it the exclusive right to bring about any modification of the provisions of refund or cancellation policy without intimidating prior notice.
